Finding Aid for the Anne Waldman Papers, 1945-2012
Anne Waldman Papers
- Audiovisual
  - Video Tapes
    - (WALDVID-26) "Anne Waldman-Assorted Singles" and "Eyes In All Heads Audio Mix": audio of Waldman, video of home shopping television channel (DVD access copy available), undated, 1 hour, 50 minutes (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-27) Anne Waldman, Michael Brownstein (?), and others in home movie, Boulder (DVD access copy available), undated, 5 minutes (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-28) Word One, #1-7, hosted by Anne Waldman: duplicate copy made by library staff in for the University of Michigan Special Collections Library exhibit, 1993, 2002, 6 hours, 51 minutes (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-29) "An Anne Waldman Anthology: Copied from Selected Videos in the Waldman Archive." Made by library staff for the University of Michigan Special Collections Library exhibit, 2002, 7 hours 10 minutes (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-30) AWS-1 Keynote Speaker, Andrei Codrescu, March 13, 2002 (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-31) AWS-2 Anne Waldman, The Early Years. Moderator: Chris Tysh, panelists: Eleni Sikelianso, Joanne Ryger, Ken Padgett, March 14, 2002 (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-32) AWS-3, "Publishings and the Small Press Scene." Moderator: Bill Morgan, panelists: Steve Clay Allan Kornblum, Ken Mikolowski, March 14, 2002 (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-33) AWS-4 "Buddist Influences, Naropa U., and the Kack Kerouac School of Diembodied Poetics." Moderator: David Cope, panelists: Laura Bardwell, Anselm Hollo, March 14, 2002 (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-34) AWS-5 Afternoon Reading featuring Andrei Codrescu, Johnny Floyd, Molly Raynor, John Liberzon, Eseohe Arhebamen, Janet Osmond, Ken Mikolowski, Antler, Akila Oliver, March 14, 2002 (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-35) AWS-6 "Evening Readings," Eleni Silelianos, Lorenzo Thomas, with introduction by Anselm Hollo, and Rachel Blau DuPlessis, Ron Padgett with introduction by Bill Morgan, March 14, 2002 (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-36) AWS-7 "Politics and Feminism." Moderator: Pamela Trotman Reid, panelists: Maria Damon, Akilah Oliver, Heather Thomas, March 15, 2002 (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-37) AWS-8 "Anne Waldman as Performer and Collaborator." Moderator: Kathryn Beam, panelists: Jena Osman, Kristin Prevallet, and Steven Taylor, March 15, 2002 (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-38) AWS-9 "Critical Overview: Anne Waldman's Role in 20th Century American Poetics." Panelists: Alan Gilbert, Rachel Blau DuPlessis and Lorenzo Thomas, March 15, 2002 (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-39) AWS-10 "Afternoon Readings." Laura Bardwell, Emily Brandt, David Cope, Dave Gardner, Katie Gill, Kristin Hatch, Mike Marcinkowski, Yukan Rymar, Heather Thomas, Chris Tysh, March 15, 2002 (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-40) AWS-11 "Evening Readings." Welcome by Peggy Daub. Mei-mei Berssenbrugee, Anselm Hollo, Joanne Kyger, Anne Waldman with Steven Taylor, March 15, 2002 (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-41) AWS-12 "Addendum I-IV." I. Anne Waldman, "Make Up On Empty Space." II. Exhibit (with Anne Waldman soundtrack). III. Library Opening Remarks. IV. Whitman's Leave of Grass, March 13-15, 2002 (Box 91)
    - (WALDVID-42) Anne Waldman at West Chester University, West Chester, Pennsylvania, 2004 (Box 91)
    - Reformatted user copies on DVD. WALDVID-1 through WALDVID-27 (Box 92)
  - DVDs
    - (WALDDVD-1) Anne Waldman and Ed Bowes, Words and Pictures, "The Menage," poem by Carl Rakosi, 2003 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDVD-2) Anne Waldman and Ed Bowes, "Colors in the Mechanism of Concealment," 2004 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDVD-3) "Transatlantic Howl!, A Dedication to Allen Ginsberg," October 14, 2004 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDVD-4) "Radical's Reunion: Rocky Flats Truth Force 10th," 2006 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDVD-5)"Buddhism and the Beat Generation with Anne Waldman," March 16, 2006 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDVD-6) Anne Waldman and Steve Taylor, "Cyborg on the Zattere," New York City, 2011 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDVD-7) American Road, ca. 2013 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDVD-8) Anne Waldman Reading at Bard, November 6, 2008 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDVD-9) Cecilia Viana reading at Bard, November 6, 2008 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDVD-10) "Naked Lunch at 50," School of Visual Arts, October 10, 2009 (Box 92)
  - Digital Files
    - (WALDDIG-1)Iovis Backup (Floppy disk), 1989 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-2) Iovis 2 (Floppy disk), 1994 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-3)Iovis 2 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-4) Iovis 2: I-VI, VII-XIV (Floppy disk), January 29, 1995 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-5) Iovis 2: I-VI, VII-XIV, New Arrangement (Floppy disk), January 29, 1995 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-6) Iovis 2: I-XIV (Floppy disk), February 28, 1995 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-7) Iovis 2, backup, I-XIV (Floppy disk), September 16, 1995 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-8) Iovis 2 backup (Floppy disk), September 18, 1995 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-9) Iovis 2 (Floppy disk), October 22, 1995 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-10) Email Correspondence, Incoming (Floppy disk), September 1997-April 1998 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG 11) Email Correspondence, Incoming (Floppy disk), April 27, 1998-July 30, 1998 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG 12) Email Correspondence, Outgoing (Floppy disk), September 17, 1997-April 24, 1998 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-13) Email Correspondence, Outgoing (Floppy disk), April 25, 1998-July 25, 1998 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-14) Email Correspondence, recent emails (Floppy disk), April 7, 1999-June 30, 1999 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-15) Email Correspondence, recent emails (Floppy disk), July 1, 1999-November 30, 1999 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-16) Email Correspondence, recent emails (Floppy disk), December 1999 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-17) Email Correspondence, recent emails (Floppy disk), January 1, 2000-February 29, 2000 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-18) Email Correspondence, recent emails (Floppy disk), March 2, 2000-April 1, 2000 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-19) Anne Waldman, Troubairitz, Eine Ubersetzung (Floppy disk), 1996 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-20) Anne Waldman and Ambrose Bali, writing (Floppy disk), 1998 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-21) Current Naropa Anthology (Floppy disk), 1999 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-22) Randy Roark (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-23) Autobiography (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-24) Writing from Powerbook (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-25) Interview with Anne Waldman (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-26) Vow to Poetry - Coffee House Press (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-27) Vow to Poetry, full file. Uncut version of text/interviews (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-28) Beat Poets and Artists, 1965 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-29) Anne Waldman's Archives and Ambrose Materials (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-30) "Kali Yuga Poetics" (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-31) Beat Files _____? Introduction (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-32-1) Civil Disobediences, A-J (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-32-2) Civil Disobediences, K-Z (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-33) Structure of the World (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-34) Poetics Book #1 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-35) 1.HD20 Global Back-up #1 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-36) 2.HD20 Global Back-up #2 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-37) 3.HD20 Global Back-up #3 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-38) 4.HD20 Global Back-up #4 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-39) 5.HD20 Global Back-up #5 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-40) 6.HD20 Global Back-up #6 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-41) 7.HD20 Global Back-up #7 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-42) 8.HD20 Global Back-up #8 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-43) 9.HD20 Global Back-up #9 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-44) 10.HD20 Global Back-up #10 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-45) 11.HD20 Global Back-up #11 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-46) 12.HD20 Global Back-up #12 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-47) 13.HD20 Global Back-up #13 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-48) 14.HD20 Global Back-up #14 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-50) 16.HD20 Global Back-up #16 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-51) 17.HD20 Global Back-up #17 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-52) 18.HD20 Global Back-up #18 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-49) 15.HD20 Global Back-up #15 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-53) 19.HD20 Global Back-up #19 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-54) 20.HD20 Global Back-up #20 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-55) 21.HD20 Global Back-up #21 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-56) 22.HD20 Global Back-up #22 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-57) 23.HD20 Global Back-up #23 (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-58) Marriage: A Sentence, pages 15, 17, 18, 58, 24, 25, for newsletter (Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-59) "A Declaration of Interdependence," Naropa Institute (Floppy disk), July 1990 (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-60) "Kerouac" lecture, (5 1/4" Floppy disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-61) Anne Waldman's Calendar (Floppy disk) (label has been placed over shutter and read-write slot), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-62) "Backup" (Zip disk), undated (Box 92)
    - (WALDDIG-63) Lisa Berman, Naropa Summer Writing Program, Western Digital My Passport Hard Drive [closed], undated (Box 92)
- Various series-Oversize
  - Oversize: Poetry Project, Naropa/Boulder, and Other, 1968-2012 (Oversize 93)
  - Oversize: Poetry Project, Naropa/Boulder, and Other, 1968-2002 (Oversize 94)
  - Oversize: Family, John Waldman, Anne Waldman scrapbook (Oversize 95)
  - Oversize: Personal, Memorabilia: T-shirts: Fast Speaking Woman shirt and two political shirts, Allen Ginsberg tribute shirt and Bowery Poetry Club cloth bag. undated (Oversize 96)
  - Oversize: Early Years, Pre-High School Scrapbook, scattered dates (Oversize 97)
  - Oversize: Printed Material
    - Anne Waldman and others (Oversize 98)
    - Miscellaneous (Map-case B, Drawer 8, Portfolio 1)
  - Oversize: Photographs
    - Photographs by Allen Ginsberg
      - Anne Waldman and William Burroughs, 1984 (Oversize 98)
      - Anne Waldman in make-up chair, 1984 (Oversize 98)
    - Naropa Institute, Allen Ginsberg Library dedication, 1993 (Oversize 98)
    - Performance, ca. 1973 (Oversize 98)
    - Portraits, 1983, undated (Oversize 98)
    - Rolling Thunder Revue, 1975 (Oversize 98)
  - Oversize: Art
    - Bradner, K.L. Paintings on paper (3), undated (Oversize 99)
    - Brown, Molly? [Anne Waldman's guess] Portrait of Carl Waldman: pencil (Oversize 99)
    - Heym, Virginia. Portrait of Anne Waldman: pencil, 1986 (Oversize 99)
    - Kean, K.K. The Byrd Hoffman School of Byrds: 18 Small Plays & a Concert: offset prints of drawings for Deafman Glance, plus painted envelope, 1973 (Oversize 99)
    - Landis/Lanois?, _______? Oil pastels: appropriated Anne Waldman flyers, undated (Oversize 99)
    - Schneeman, George. Portrait of Anne Waldman: print (3 copies), undated (Oversize 99)
    - Schneeman, George. Collage, 1969 (Oversize 99)
    - Schneeman, George. Foxes in the Henhouse, 2004 (Oversize 99)
    - Schneeman, George and Anne Waldman. Homage to Allen G. Portfolio of copies of sketches, 1997 (Oversize 99)
    - Schneeman, George and Michael Brownstein. Ninth Symphony: print, with poem by Michael Brownstein, 1972 (Oversize 99)
    - Schneeman, George and Eileen Myles. For Reed: print, 256/275, with poem by Eileen Myles, 1979 (Oversize 99)
    - Schneeman, George. Print of blue and green shirts, undated (Oversize 99)
    - Schneeman, George. Landscape, labeled "#5": watercolor, 1995 (Oversize 99)
    - Wilkie, Britton. Anne Waldman: paint on paper, 1972 (Oversize 99)
    - Schneeman, George. Calendars: Eight prints, 1970-1984 (Oversize 99)
    - Waldman, Anne (?). Prints (6), undated (Oversize 100)
    - Waldman, Anne. Instrument of General Disarmament: drawing and collage with text (Oversize 100)
    - Braindard, Joe. Portrait of Anne Waldman: pencil, ca. 1967 (Oversize 100)
    - Rotenberg, Tina. Portrait of Anne Waldman: pencil, 1998 (Oversize 100)
    - Waldman, Anne. Collage on cardboard, with elephant, undated (Oversize 100)
    - Wilkie, Britton. "For the Waldmans/--my hotel room in Luxembourg/with love from Britt Wilkie/Spring 1977": watercolor, 1977 (Oversize 100)
    - Wilkie, Britton. Pen & ink drawing, "p.22": spaceship and baby, undated (Oversize 100)
    - Wilkie, Britton. "Oil Painting Sec. 1.": still life, oil painting, undated (Oversize 100)
    - Wilkie, Britton. Labeled "9": watercolor, undated (Oversize 100)
    - "Lucentio": paint & collage, childhood drawing, undated (Oversize 100)
    - Unidentified. Prints of birds, mythological creature (2), undated (Oversize 100)
    - Sree Jagannathji engravings, India, undated (Oversize 100)
    - Unidentified. Designs on a pink background: prints, undated (Oversize 100)
    - Corso, Gregory. Anne ghost drawing: pen and ink, undated (Oversize 101)
    - Corso, Gregory. Portrait of Anne Waldman on notepaper (Oversize 101)
    - Duncan, Robert. "Bombay Gin" drawing: pen and ink, 1976-1978? (Oversize 101)
    - Wilkie, Britton. "Mechanicals" book layout pages [by Britton Wilkie?], undated (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Bowes, Ed. Moving by Bernadette May er: photographs with Anne Waldman's editorial notes, published 1971 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Brainard, Joe. West Indies Poems by Anne Waldman: pen & ink, cover and other illustrations, published 1972 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Burckhardt, Rudy. Rocky Ledge 6: pen & ink drawings, undated (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Erbacher, Bruce. Bronze Age by Susan Noel: original and draft, published 1981 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Hamlin, Louise. Blue Mosque by Anne Waldman: watercolor, 1988 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Hiler, Jerome. Some Magic at the Dump by Reed Bye: drawing, published 1978 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Schneeman, George. Airplanes by Tom Clark: pen & ink, published ca. 1966 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Schneeman, George. Oranges by Frank O'Hara: pen & ink, plus reproduction, published ca. 1969-1970 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Schneeman, George. Limousine Kids on the Ground by Elizabeth Fox: pen & ink plus reproductions, published 1983 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Schneeman, George. Parade of the Caterpillars by Larry Fagin, published 1968 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Schneeman, George. Ted Berrigan: An Annotated Checklist: color proof only, ca. 1998 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Schneeman, George. Young Manhattan different cover versions and invoice, 1998-1999 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Schneeman, George. Gasper Still in His Cage by Reed Bye, rejected cover, undated (Oversize 101)
    - Thomas, Cecilio. Fit Music by Lorenzo Thomas: photocopy (?) reproduction, published 1970 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Clark, Tom. The World 11 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Clark, Tom. The World #? (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Fagin, Larry. The World 10 (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Goldberg, Mike. The World 16: felt tip pen & collage (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Goldberg, Mike. Alternate design for The World 16: pencil (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Jacquette, Yvonne. The World 21: pen and ink, undated (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Mayer, Rosemary? [Anne Waldman's guess.] Drawings for Rocky Ledge cover (2): pen & ink (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, Veitch, Rick. The World 15: pen & ink (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, mimeograph reproductions, The World 24: Pat Padgett (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, mimeograph reproductions, The World 25: Joe Brainard (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, mimeograph reproductions, The World 30: Larry Rivers (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, mimeograph reproductions, The World 28: Alex Katz (Oversize 101)
    - Cover art, mimeograph reproductions, The World 26: Mimi Gross (Oversize 101)
    - Brainard, Joe. Unfinished collaboration with Anne Waldman and Reed Bye: pen & ink (Oversize 102)
    - Cover art, collaborations, O My Life!, Schneeman, George. Cover: pen & ink, undated (Oversize 102)
    - Cover art, collaborations for O My Life!, Waldman, Anne. Print done while at Bennington College, Vincent Longo, instructor (Oversize 102)
    - Cover art, collaborations, Proofs for O My Life! (Oversize 102)
      (May includes other materials)
    - Cover art, collaborations, Brainard, Joe; Dennis, Donna; Schneeman, George; Waldman, Anne; et al.? No Hassles: drawings and photographs, published 1971 (Oversize 102)
    - Flyer/poster art, Jacquette, Yvonne. Kenneth Koch at St. Marks Church in-the-Bowery (Oversize 102)
    - Flyer/poster art, Schneeman, George. Announcement for Iovis II: pen & ink, 1997 (Oversize 102)
    - Flyer/poster art, Schneeman, George and Waldman, Anne. "Poet's Giant Christmas Celebration," undated (Oversize 102)
    - Flyer/poster art, Schneeman, George. Michael Brownstein and Vito Hannibal Acconci reading: pen & ink, undated (Oversize 102)
    - Flyer/poster art, [Schneeman, George?] "John Wieners at St. Marks Church in-the-Bouwerie," undated (Oversize 102)
    - Unidentified, Newspaper collages, 1983, undated (Oversize 102)
    - Cover art, Schneeman, George. Four Travels by Reed Bye and Anne Waldman: pen & ink with glued-on pieces, published 1979 (Oversize 103)
    - Cover art, Schneeman, George. Half a Tourist by Annie Witkowski: pen & ink, published 1980 (Oversize 103)
    - Waldman, Anne (?). Prints (51), undated (Oversize 103)
    - Hunter, Maureen. Two Portraits of Anne Waldman: prints (for cover of Kill or Cure), undated (Oversize 103)
    - Hunter, Maureen. Image for Robert Hunter book, Penguin: print, undated (Oversize 103)
    - Sikelianos, Gina. Watercolor, undated (Oversize 103)
    - Wilkie, Britton. Woodcut prints of man, man & giraffe (2), undated (Oversize 103)
    - Wilkie, Britton. Icon, labeled "??????" (Michael): painting on wood, undated (Oversize 103)
    - Waldman, Anne. In June: collage & painting with text "As fine disc sinks over blue Rocky, daughter thinks of father's birthday," inscription on back reads "for Daddy--with much love, Anne, June 1980" (Oversize 103)
    - Unidentified. Watercolor with stampings, undated (Oversize 103)
    - Cover art, Schneeman, George. The World 3, 8, 12: pen & ink (Oversize 104)
    - Cover art, Schneeman, George. The World #?: pen & ink, and plastic film (Oversize 104)
    - Cover art, Boyce, Jack. The World 5, 15 cover design: pen & ink, conti crayon (Oversize 104)
    - Cover art, Dennis, Donna. The World 17: photograph (Oversize 104)
    - Jacquette, Yvonne. Signed print: photocopy, door and tile, 1968 (Oversize 104)
    - Flyer/poster art, Rothstein, S. Poster for Empire State College poetry reading by Anne Waldman: pen, colored pencil, June 1976 (Oversize 104)
    - Brainard, Joe. Some Notes on Doing a Cover Design for "Highway to the Sky" by Michael Brownstein: pastel & other media (Oversize 105)
      (inscribed "For Anne with love, Joe")
    - Brainard, Joe. Original postcard with cigarette: watercolor, undated (Oversize 105)
    - D'Arcangelo, Allan. "Work for Anne Waldman": color photocopy of three artworks, 1997 (Oversize 105)
    - Cover art, Murray, Elizabeth. Her Story by Anne Waldman and Elizabeth Murray: cover art proofs, published 1990 (Oversize 105)
    - Jacquette, Yvonne. "Rt. 1 Intersection: 180 degrees": Hand-colored Xerox, 1978 (Oversize 106)
    - Notley, Alice. "Archaic" watercolor of heart, 1987 (Oversize 106)
    - Schiffin, Herb. Three Worlds, inscribed "'three Worlds' 1972--for Anne": painting on canvas, 1972 (Oversize 106)
    - Mikolowski, Ann. Miniature oil painting on linen of Allen Ginsberg and Anne Waldman, 1988 (Oversize 107)
    - Mask of Anne Waldman's face, 1980 (Oversize 107)
    - Ritcheson, Amber. Portraits of Anne Waldman and others on tiles with hemp string, undated (Oversize 107)
    - Waldman, Anne. Large textured print, black-and-white, undated (Oversize 108)
    - Waldman, Carl. Painting with glued-on objects, undated (Oversize 108)
    - Waldman, Anne (?). Prints (15), undated (Oversize 108)
    - Corso, Gregory; Ginsberg, Allen; McClure, Michael; Waldman, Anne; Whalen, Philip. Five/I/'77: 5 lithographed sheets and cover, 1977 (Oversize 108)
    - Dermisache, Mertha. Diario No. 1 Año 1, limited-run serial publication, offset print, 1972 (Oversize 108)
    - Gordon, Louise. Still life: crayon, undated (Oversize 108)
    - Pozzi, Gianantonio. why isn't she here yet?: pen & ink, 1977 (Map-case B, Drawer 8, Portfolio 2)